A Finding Aid to the Fendrick Gallery Records, 1952-2001, in the Archives of American Art AAA.fendgall
Archives of American Art
Fendrick Gallery records
1952-2001
AAA.fendgall
Archives of American Art
105.2 Linear feet
The records of the Fendrick Gallery measure 105.2 linear feet and span the years 1952 to 2001. The bulk of the collection is comprised of artist's files that document the gallery's relations with and representation of over 300 contemporary artists and sculptors, including Robert Arneson, William Bailey, Daniel Brush, Wendell Castle, Robert Cottingham, James Drake, John Dreyfuss, Walter Dusenbury, Roger Essley, Helen Frankenthaler, Sam Gilliam, Jasper Johns, Raymond Kaskey, Claude and Francois Lalanne, Albert Paley, Joseph Raffael, Carol Summer, and numerous other artists. Also found are subject, exhibition, commission, administrative, and financial files, as well as files documenting the gallery's relationship with other museums and galleries.
Fendrick Gallery
Historical Note
The Fendrick Gallery was established in 1960 as a "by appointment only" gallery out of Barbara Fendrick's Washington, D.C. area home. Initially the gallery promoted contemporary American and European prints by emerging artists and also commissioned print editions by nationally known artists. During the mid 1960s, the Fendrick Gallery also coordinated and produced art exhibitions on a contract basis for the United States Information Agency. The gallery was responsible for organizing the first large American art exhibition at the Department of State and the Federal Reserve.
In May, 1970 the Fendrick Gallery moved into a three-story townhouse in Georgetown and began presenting regular exhibitions open to the public. The gallery offered many prominent American artists, such as Robert Arneson, Jim Dine, Helen Frankenthaler, Jasper Johns, Louise Nevelson, and Robert Rauschenberg their first solo shows in the nation's capital. The Fendrick Gallery also represented many nationally known sculptors, such as John Dreyfuss, Walter Dusenbery, Raymond Kaskey, and Albert Paley.
Over the years, Fendrick Gallery promoted many emerging artists who were breaking down the barriers between art and craft in the areas of clay, furniture, metal, and book arts. The gallery held the first major show of contemporary ceramics on the East Coast, with the 1976 exhibition, Clay USA. The gallery also received critical acclaim for its exhibitions in the area of "book arts" and held four shows featuring the works of prominent American and international book artists.
In 1987 and 1988, the gallery expanded and opened the Barbara Fendrick Gallery in the Soho section of New York City. The New York location operated as both a gallery space and storage area and was often referred to as "The Warehouse." Both the Fendrick Gallery and the Barbara Fendrick Gallery closed in the summer of 1991, but Barbara Fendrick continues to work as an art consultant, appraiser, exhibition juror, lecturer, and guest curator.
Scope and Content Note
The records of the Fendrick Gallery measure 105.2 linear feet and span the years 1952 to 2001. The bulk of the collection is comprised of artist's files that document the gallery's relationships with and representation of over 300 contemporary artists, including Robert Arneson, William Bailey, Daniel Brush, Wendell Castle, Robert Cottingham, James Drake, John Dreyfuss, Walter Dusenbury, Roger Essley, Helen Frankenthaler, Sam Gilliam, Jasper Johns, Raymond Kaskey, Claude and Francois Lalanne, Albert Paley, Joseph Raffael, Carol Summer, and numerous other artists. Also found are subject, exhibition, commission, administrative, and financial files, as well as files documenting the gallery's relationship with other museums and galleries.
Series 1, Artist's Files, measures almost 42 linear feet and dates from 1962-2001. Found here are files documenting the gallery's relationship with over 300 contemporary artists. Files typically contain correspondence, sales receipts, printed materials, exhibition catalogs and announcements, commission information, photographs, slides, and other materials.
Series 2, Albert Paley, 1970-2001, and undated, provides detailed documentation (14.5 linear feet) of the Fendrick gallery's representation of prominent American metal sculptor Albert Paley. The gallery represented Paley from the early 1980s through the early 1990s and devoted a great deal of its resources promoting Paley's work through exhibitions and commissioned sales. Correspondence between the Fendrick Galleries and Paley Studios is found in this series, along with publicity materials, commission proposals and sketches, exhibition materials, and audio-visual and photographic documentation of Paley's work. Researchers should also consult Series 3 for additional documentation of Paley's commissioned projects.
Series 3, Commissioned Works and Projects, 1972-2000, and undated, documents the variety of commissions and special projects the gallery arranged and managed on behalf of its represented artists. Because privately commissioned work and government-sponsored public art projects represented a significant source of revenue for the Fendrick galleries, the gallery devoted a substantial amount of time and resources towards securing these projects. These files contain applications, proposals, sketches, correspondence, photographs and other material arranged by name of project.
Series 4, Exhibition Files, 1961, 1970-1996, and undated, houses files relating to exhibitions organized by Fendrick Gallery. Found here are exhibition announcements, invitations, and catalogs; specific named exhibition files; and files concerning special projects or exhibitions, often jointly curated with other galleries or institutions. The Fendrick gallery was also actively involved in various governmental programs, such as Art in the Embassies Program, and organized traveling exhibits or loaned artwork to them.
The gallery's relationships with other galleries, museums, institutions, and art organizations is documented in Series 5, Museums and Galleries Files, 1952-2000, and undated. Many of the files concern loans, exhibition venues, and joint exhibitions or projects.
Series 6, Subject Files, 1952, 1960-2001, and undated contain numerous files arranged by subject heading. Here, researchers will find information collected and maintained by the gallery on various art medium, artists of interest, exhibition catalogs from museums and other galleries, information about small and fine art presses. Of particular interest are several folders entitled "Fine Art Printers & Publishers." Barbara Fendrick's early years in the art business centered upon exhibiting, promoting, and selling prints produced by young, emerging American artists. The information found here documents her growing personal relationships with some of the most prominent artists and printmakers of this era.
Records documenting administrative, business, operating, and financial affairs are arranged in Series 7, Administrative and Financial Files, 1960-2001, and undated. Found here are records of both the Barbara Fendrick Gallery (New York) and the Fendrick Gallery (Washington, D.C.), as well as files that document Barbara Fendrick's role as art consultant, appraiser, lecturer, exhibition juror, and guest curator. Found are numerous inventory cards, insurance records, consignment files, general correspondence, lists, loan files, notebooks, real estate files, card files on artists and clients, and history files. Of particular interest are the Day Books/Dailies maintained by the New York gallery staff consisting of entries and notes regarding prospective clients and their interests. The Telephone Log Books contain details of telephone conversations with artists, clients, dealers, and other art professionals. Series 7 also houses the financial records of both galleries, including invoices, financial statements, expenses, accounts, and tax records.
Arrangement
The Fendrick Gallery records were processed to the series, subseries, and folder level. The collection is arranged into seven series. Items within folders, for the most part, were not fully sorted or preserved. When possible, materials were generally arranged at least by year. Within Series 1, Artists' Files, each set of folders for a particular artist are only given span dates. Due to the amount and complexity of material compiled on the artist Albert Paley, his files are arranged into a separate series of their own.
Series 1: Artists Files, 1962-2001, undated (Box 1-42, OV 108-110; 41.5 linear ft.)
Series 2: Albert Paley, 1970-2001, undated (Box 42-54; Box 107, OV 111-113, 117-118; 14.5 linear ft.)
Series 3: Commissioned Works and Projects, 1972- 2000, undated (Box 54-57; 3.5 linear ft.)
Series 4: Exhibition Files, 1961, 1970-1996, undated (Box 58-63; 5.5 linear feet)
Series 5: Museums and Galleries Files, 1952-200, undated (Box 64-73; 9.25 linear feet)
Series 6: Subject Files, 1952, 1960-2001, undated (Box 73-88, OV 115-116; 15.5 linear ft.)
Series 7: Administrative and Financial Files, undated (Box 88-106; OV)
Provenance
The records of the Fendrick Gallery were donated to the Archives of American Art by Barbara Fendrick in 1999, with an addition to the records in 2001.
Restrictions on Access
The collection is open for research. Use of unmicrofilmed material requires an appointment.
Arneson, Robert, 1930-1992; Bailey, William, 1930-; Barbara Fendrick Gallery.; Benes, Barton Lidic; Brush, Daniel; Castle, Wendell, 1932-; Cottingham, Robert, 1935-; Drake, James, 1946-; Dreyfuss, John, 1949-; Dusenbery, Walter, 1939-; Frankenthaler, Helen, 1928-2011; Gilliam, Sam; Johns, Jasper, 1930-; Kaskey, Raymond J., 1943-; Lalanne, Claude; Lalanne, François Xavier; Maria da Conceição; Nanette L. Laitman Documentation Project for Craft and Decorative Arts in America; Paley, Albert; Raffael, Joseph, 1933-; Summer, Carol; Tenneson, Joyce, 1945-; Woodyard, William; Account books; Art galleries, Commercial--Washington (D.C.); Art, Modern--20th century--Washington (D.C.); Art--Washington (D.C.); Artists' books; Artists--Washington (D.C.); Furniture designers; Jewelers; Metal-workers; Painters; Photographs; Printmakers; Sculptors
- Artists Files, 1962-2001, undated; Series 1; (Box 1-42, OV 108-110; 41.5 linear ft.)
  Scope and Contents note
  The files contained within this series contain correspondence, photographs, slides, occasional study drawings, exhibition and commission materials, and financial materials relating to the representation and sale of individual artists' work. Arrangement is alphabetical by surname of the artist. Occasionally artists' entries are broken down further by type of material. Each letter of the alphabet also has a Miscellaneous section for materials on artists for which the gallery did not establish a file.
  - Adams, Ansel, 1974, 1984-1986 (Box 1)
  - Albers, Joseph, 1965-1976; (2 folders) (Box 1)
  - Amory, Joseph, 1972-1988, undated; (4 folders) (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Kenneth, 1982-1988, undated (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Sally, 1982-1988, undated (Box 1)
  - Antreasian, Garo, 1962-1985, undated (Box 1)
  - Anuszkiewicz, Richard, 1967-1982, undated (Box 1)
  - Arakawa, 1965-1979, undated (Box 1)
  - Akaki, Takako, 1982-1990, undated (Box 1)
  - Amitage, Kenneth, 1972-1984, undated (Box 1)
  - Armstrong, Hamilton Reed, 1964-1984, undated (Box 1)
  - Arneson, Robert, 1966-2001, undated; (2 folders) (Box 1)
  - Arneson, Robert, 1966-2001, undated; (8 folders) (Box 2)
  - Arnold, Chester, 1971-1990, undated; (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Assael, Steven, 1989-2001; (4 folders) (Box 2)
  - A, Miscellaneous, 1967-1990, undated (Box 2)
  - Bader, Gretta, 1979-1985, undated (Box 2)
  - Baer, Rod, 1984-1990, undated (Box 2)
  - Bailey, William, 1973-1999, undated; (7 folders) (Box 3)
  - Banks, Ron, 1981-1997, undated; (3 folders) (Box 3)
  - Bart, Harriett, 1988-1993, undated (Box 3)
  - Baychar, 1984-1988, undated (Box 3)
  - Beal, Jack, 1977-1987 (Box 3)
  - Beaton, Cecil, 1973-1975, undated (Box 3)
  - Benes, Barton, 1968-1999, undated; (14 folders) (Box 4)
  - Bennet, Gary Knox, 1989-1990, undated (Box 4)
  - Benson, Patricia, 1969-1979, undated; (3 folders) (Box 4)
  - Bentley, Celeste, 1986-1990, undated (Box 5)
  - Berlin, Nancy, 1989-1991, undated (Box 5)
  - Ben Tré Howard, 1982-1987 (Box 5)
  - Berns, Ben, 1966-1973, undated (Box 5)
  - Birmelin, Robert, 1976-1991, undated; (6 folders) (Box 5)
  - Bishop, Jacqueline, 1980-1990, undated; (3 folders) (Box 5)
  - Bliss, Anna Campbell, 1980-1984, undated (Box 5)
  - Bofill, Ricardo, 1985-1987, undated; (2 folders) (Box 5)
  - Boshier, Derek, 1986-1990 (Box 5)
  - Bowman, John, 1989, undated (Box 5)
  - Boyd, Evans, 1976-1981, undated (Box 5)
  - Brady, Caroline, 1977-1990, undated (Box 5)
  - Braunstein, Terry, 1978-1995, undated (Box 5)
  - Brown, David Lee, 1974-1986, undated (Box 5)
  - Brown, Roger, 1979-1989, undated; (4 folders) (Box 6)
  - Brush, Daniel, 1974-1998, undated; (8 folders) (Box 6)
  - Butterfield, Deborah, 1979-1987, undated (Box 6)
  - B, Miscellaneous, 1971-1998, undated; (4 folders) (Box 6)
  - Campbell, Graham, 1985-1991, undated (Box 6)
  - Carter, Jay, 1983-1985, undated (Box 7)
  - Carter, Yvonne, 1975-1987, undated; (4 folders) (Box 7)
  - Castanis, Muriel, 1986-1992, undated (Box 7)
  - Castle, Wendell (Box 7)
    - Accounts, 1978-1991, undated; (2 folders) (Box 7)
    - Biographical, 1976-1993, undated; (3 folders) (Box 7)
    - Catalogs, circa 1980-1990, undated (Box 7)
    - Clocks, 1979-1988 (Box 7)
    - Commissions, 1979-1992 (Box 7)
    - Correspondence, 1975-2000, undated; (7 folders) (Box 7)
    - Designs and Sketches, undated (Box 7)
    - Exhibitions, 1978-1991, undated; (2 folders) (Box 8)
    - Loans and Consignments, 1981-1991 (Box 8)
    - Materials, 1977-1989, undated (Box 8)
    - Notes and Miscellaneous, undated (Box 8)
    - Printed Material, 1968, 1977-1997, undated; (9 folders) (Box 8)
    - Publicity, undated (Box 8)
    - Sales, 1978-1987, undated; (2 folders) (Box 8)
    - Workshop and School, 1984-1989, undated; (2 folders) (Box 8)
    - Photographs and Slides, undated; (6 folders) (Box 9)
  - Chihuly, Dale, 1979-1989, undated (Box 9)
  - Clark, Emery, 1981-1988, undated (Box 9)
  - Clark, Michael, 1977-1987, undated (Box 9)
  - Close, Chuck, 1978-1998; (3 folders) (Box 9)
  - Cole, Willie, 1989-1991, undated (Box 9)
  - Conceição, Maria da (See same series, São) (Box 9)
  - Cooney Crawford, Thom, 1984-1991, undated; (4 folders) (Box 9)
  - Cooper, Michael, 1976-1986, undated; (2 folders) (Box 9)
  - Cooper, Stephanie, 1980-1983 (Box 9)
  - Cornell, Baird, 1985-1989; (2 folders) (Box 9)
  - Cottingham, Robert, 1980-2001, undated; (14 folders) (Box 10)
  - Cox, Solveig, 1987-1991, undated (Box 10)
  - Curry, Kate, 1987-1991, undated (Box 10)
  - Curry, Kate, 1987-1991, undated (Box 11)
  - Curtis, E.S., 1926, 1928, undated (Box 11)
  - Curtis, Timothy, 1984-1990, undated (Box 11)
  - C, Miscellaneous, 1970-1999, undated; (4 folders) (Box 11)
  - Danko, Peter, 1977-1991, undated (Box 11)
  - Danziger, Joan, 1972-1985, undated; (2 folders) (Box 11)
  - Davenport, Rebecca, 1972-1986, undated; (3 folders) (Box 11)
  - Davis, Gene, 1972-1985 (Box 11)
  - De Forest, Roy, 1972-1993, undated; (2 folders) (Box 11)
  - Devore, Richard, 1973-1989, undated (Box 11)
  - Dickson, John, 1978-1984 (Box 12)
  - Dine, Jim, 1968-1979, undated; (3 folders) (Box 12)
  - Douglas, David, 1984-1987 (Box 12)
  - Drake, James, 1981-1999, undated; (10 folders) (Box 12)
  - Dreyfuss, John (Box 13)
    - General, 1981-1999, undated; (20 folders) (Box 13)
    - General, 1981-1999, undated; (6 folders) (Box 14)
    - Exhibition, Diamonds are Forever: Artists and Writers on Baseball, 1989, undated; (2 folders) (Box 14)
    - Northern Telecom Inc., 1989, undated (Box 14)
    - Susquehanna Art Museum, 1990-1995, undated (Box 14)
  - DuBourg, Robert, 1976-1987, undated; (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Durand, Lucien, 1972-1988, undated (Box 14)
  - Dusenbery, Walter (Box 15)
    - Carl Freeman, Gaithersburg, MD, 1986-1991, undated (Box 15)
    - Commission Rejections, 1987-1991, undated (Box 15)
    - General, 1980-1997, undated; (16 folders) (Box 15)
    - Mast Industries, Inc., Andover, MA, 1986-1989, undated (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous Commission Proposals, 1985-1992, undated (Box 15)
    - Walter Dusenbery: Classical Forms (1986), Washington, D.C., 1985-1989, undated (Box 16)
  - D, Miscellaneous, 1971-2000, undated; (2 folders) (Box 16)
  - Elmore, Ray, 1973-1979, undated (Box 16)
  - Epes, Maria, 1977-1981, undated (Box 16)
  - Erlebacher, Martha, Mayer, 1980-1990, undated; (2 folders) (Box 16)
  - Ess, Barbara, 1980-1994, undated (Box 16)
  - Essley, Roger, 1979-1992, undated; (8 folders) (Box 16)
  - Evans, Donald, 1966-1990, undated (Box 16)
  - Eversley, Frederick, 1974-1984, undated (Box 16)
  - E, Miscellaneous, 1975-1990, undated (Box 16)
  - Feltus, Allan, 1973-1987, undated (Box 16)
  - Ficalora, Michael, 1983-1989, undated (Box 16)
  - Flack, Audrey, 1986-1993, undated; (2 folders) (Box 17)
  - Flanagan, Michael, 1981-1993, undated (Box 17)
  - Fleming, Frank, 1979-1991, undated; (4 folders) (Box 17)
  - Ford, James, 1988-1992, undated; (2 folders) (Box 17)
  - Forrester, Patricia, 1976-2001, undated; (6 folders) (Box 17)
  - Forrester, Patricia, 1976-2001, undated (Box 18)
  - Fraga, Ed, 1989-1991, undated (Box 18)
  - Francis, Ke, 1987-1991, undated (Box 18)
  - Frankenthaler, Helen, 1969-2000, undated; (7 folders) (Box 18)
  - Friedman, Alan, 1976-1989, undated (Box 18)
  - Fraser, Scott, 1989-1990 (Box 18)
  - Freckelton, Sondra, 1978-1991, undated (Box 18)
  - Freud, Lucien, 1989-1996, undated (Box 18)
  - Frost, Adrian & Jan Gallione, 1987-1991, undated (Box 18)
  - Fuller, Buckminster, 1974-1985, undated (Box 18)
  - F, Miscellaneous, 1982-1995, undated; (2 folders) (Box 18)
  - Gallione, Jan, & Frost, Adrian, 1989-1990 (Box 19)
  - Gerwirz, Nancy, 1988-1996 (Box 19)
  - Gilhooly, David, 1974-1984, undated (Box 19)
  - Gill, Bryan, 1990-1991, undated (Box 19)
  - Gillespie, Dorothy, 1979, undated (Box 19)
  - Gilliam, Sam (Box 19)
    - Accounts, 1972-1991, undated; (2 folders) (Box 19)
    - Agreements, 1973, 1978, n.d (Box 19)
    - Audio-Visual Material, undated (Box 19)
    - Bibliography, undated (Box 19)
    - Biographical, circa 1971-circa 1999, n.d (Box 19)
    - Catalogs, 1975-1999, undated (Box 19)
    - Commissions (Box 19)
      - LaGuardia Airport Central Terminal Building, Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, New York, N.Y. (See also OV 108), 1991-1996, undated; (2 folders) (Box 19)
      - Miscellaneous Projects, 1974-1992, undated (Box 19)
    - Consignments, 1974-1991, undated (Box 19)
    - Correspondence, General, 1969-2000, undated; (7 folders) (Box 19)
    - Exhibitions (Box 19)
      - New Paintings by Sam Gilliam, Dart Gallery, Chicago, Ill., 1976-1977, undated (Box 19)
      - Paintings, Watercolors, Prints by Sam Gilliam, Collectors' Gallery, Stevenson, Md., 1975-1976, undated (Box 20)
      - Sam Gilliam, An Exhibition of Paintings, Rutgers University Art Gallery, Rutgers University, New Brunswick, N.J., 1975-1977, undated (Box 20)
      - Sam Gilliam, Extensions, Part One, Anderson Gallery, Virginia Commonwealth University, Richmond, Va., 1977-1978 (Box 20)
      - Sam Gilliam, Paintings Watercolors, Prints, Linda Farris Gallery, Seattle, Wash., 1974-1976, undated (Box 20)
      - Sam Gilliam Retrospective, Greenberg Gallery, St. Louis, Mo., 1972-1975, undated (Box 20)
      - Miscellaneous, 1970-1995, undated; (4 folders) (Box 20)
      - Nina Freudenheim Gallery, Buffalo, N.Y., 1976-1978, undated (Box 20)
    - J. B. Speed Art Museum, Lexington, Ken., 1975-1976, undated (Box 20)
    - Loans, 1966-1991, n.d (Box 20)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1971-1991, undated (Box 20)
    - Notes & Miscellaneous, 1971-1990, undated; (4 folders) (Box 20)
    - Photographs, undated; (5 folders) (Box 20)
    - Printed Material, 1966-1995, n.d (Box 21)
    - Publicity, 1972-1997, undated (Box 21)
    - Rapoport Printing Corp., 1975. n.d (Box 21)
    - Reviews, 1970-1996, undated (Box 21)
    - Sales (Box 21)
      - Carl Solway Gallery, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1972-1976, undated (Box 21)
      - Miscellaneous, 1972-1993, undated; (2 folders) (Box 21)
      - Phoenix Art Gallery, San Francisco, Calif., 1972-1976, undated (Box 21)
    - Slides, undated (Box 21)
    - Trust Fund for Daughters, 1978, undated (Box 21)
    - Twinrocker (Papermakers), 1973, undated (Box 21)
    - University of Cincinnati, 1998-2000, undated (Box 21)
    - University of Florida, 1988-1989, undated (Box 21)
  - Greenwald, Caroline, 1977-1987, undated; (2 folders) (Box 22)
  - Grooms, Red, 1971-1991, undated (Box 22)
  - G, Miscellaneous, 1970-1998, undated; (3 folders) (Box 22)
  - Haas, Richard, 1985-1986, undated (Box 22)
  - Hahn, Judith, undated (Box 22)
  - Halpern, Sylvia, 1982-1984, undated (Box 22)
  - Hamisky, Kim, 1985-1986, undated (Box 22)
  - Han, H.N., 1989-1991, undated (Box 22)
  - Harlow, Malcolm, 1984-1985, undated (Box 22)
  - Harper, Link, undated (Box 22)
  - Hart, Frederick, 1979-2000, undated; (3 folders) (Box 22)
  - Heller, Frank, undated (Box 22)
  - Hill, Robin, undated (Box 22)
  - Hockney, David, 1973-1991, undated (Box 22)
  - Hoffman, Hans, 1973-1976, undated (Box 22)
  - Hnizdovsky, Jacques, 1962-1989, undated (Box 22)
  - Hnizdovsky, Jacques, 1962-1989, undated; (4 folders) (Box 23)
  - Huddy, Margaret, 1984-1991, undated (Box 23)
  - H, Miscellaneous, 1968-1997, undated; (6 folders) (Box 23)
  - Indiana, Robert, 1971-1976, undated (Box 23)
  - Inglese, Judith, 1976-1992, undated; (2 folders) (Box 23)
  - I, Miscellaneous, 1967-1990, undated; (2 folders) (Box 24)
  - James, Derek, 1989-1996, undated (Box 24)
  - Jeanclos, Georges, 1986, undated (Box 24)
  - Jenkins, Paul, 1977-1981 (Box 24)
  - Jessup, Robert, 1983-1989, undated (Box 24)
  - Jimenez, Luis, 1980-1991, undated (Box 24)
  - Johns, Jasper, 1973-1993, undated; (5 folders) (Box 24)
  - Johnson, J. Seward, 1982-1990, undated; (2 folders) (Box 24)
  - Johnston, Barry, 1984-1988, undated (Box 24)
  - Joyle, Jeff, 1988-1991, undated (Box 24)
  - J, Miscellaneous, 1971-1991, undated; (2 folders) (Box 24)
  - Kaskey, Raymond (Box 24)
    - Accounts, 1986-1998, undated (Box 24)
    - Audio/Visual material, 1985, 1995, undated (Box 24)
    - Biographical, circa 1986-1997, undated (Box 24)
    - Commissions, Miscellaneous, 1985-1997, undated (Box 25)
    - Correspondence, General, 1983-2001, undated; (3 folders) (Box 25)
    - Court House/Federal Building, Shreveport, La., 1993-1997, undated (Box 25)
    - Franklin C. Salisbury Building, Bethesda, Md., 1985-1988, undated (Box 25)
    - Harold Washington Library Center and Lincoln Properties for Winter Garden, Chicago, Ill., 1987-1990, undated (Box 25)
    - Maryland Department of Agriculture, Annapolis, Md., 1986-1990, undated (Box 25)
    - National Building Museum, Washington, D.C., 1991-1996, undated (Box 25)
    - Notes and Miscellaneous, 1980-1996, undated (Box 25)
    - Photographs and Slides, undated (Box 25)
    - Portland Building and U.S. Courthouse, Portland, Ore., 1984-1989, undated (Box 25)
    - "Portlandia Over Portland," Dissertation, 1989 (Box 25)
    - Portlandia Sculpture, Portland, Ore., 1984-1988 (Box 25)
    - Printed Material, 1984-1991, undated (Box 25)
    - Proposals and Applications, Miscellaneous, 1984-1996, undated; (3 folders) (Box 25)
  - Kaskey, Sherry, 1989-1990, undated (Box 26)
  - Kaslow, Lisa, 1991-1993, undated (Box 26)
  - Katz, Alex, 1971-1974, 1978-1979, undated (Box 26)
  - Katz, Alex, Photographs, undated (circa 1975?) (Box 26)
  - Katzen, Lila, 1988-1989, undated (Box 26)
  - Kaufman, Emily, 1984-1986, undated (Box 26)
  - Kehl, Richard, 1989-1990, undated (Box 26)
  - Kelly, Ellsworth, Photographs & Slides, undated (Box 26)